{
    "id": "b45aa8ae91214362b675c5f3e444e9a1",
    "title": "Present perfect continuous tense exercise",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "98a617880f124bf7a5bbcdfadf82a4a5",
            "title": "Present Perfect Continuous Tenses Exercise",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "How long ...................................... for?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "are you waiting",
                        "have you been waiting",
                        "have you waited"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "We ........................................ in this street for twenty years.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "are living",
                        "have been living",
                        "live"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "He ........................................... in the garden since morning.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "is working",
                        "has been working",
                        "work"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "It ....................................... since yesterday.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "is raining",
                        "rained",
                        "has been raining"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "I .................................................... this laptop for three years.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "am using",
                        "use",
                        "have been using"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "The workers ......................................... higher wages for a long time.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "has been demanding",
                        "have been demanding",
                        "demand"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "The girl .......................................... her lessons.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "has been learning",
                        "have been learning",
                        "had been learning"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "The children ................................................. in the garden.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "has been playing",
                        "have been playing",
                        "had been playing"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "‘You look tired.’ ‘Yes, I ............................................’",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "am running",
                        "have been running",
                        "has been running"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Who .............................................. in my bed?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "is sleeping",
                        "has been sleeping",
                        "have been sleeping"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}